<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>wedding on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/wedding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wedding on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Haste to the wedding: the musical interlude</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-music/</guid>
      <description>Amongst the hasty planning of our wedding, it occurred to us that I could provide a musical interlude on the tin whistle that I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning to play over the last 18 months or so. I was initially a bit hesitant about this (can we say reluctant&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haste to the wedding (II): the day</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-ii/</guid>
      <description>Where were we; oh yes, we were eloping to Scotland. Wow. It’s still a little scary to think it. And it’s getting even harder to write about. But here’s part two of the ‘haste to the wedding’ story, from leaving home until the end of the wedding day. And for those who don’t know the reason these posts are entitled ‘haste to the wedding’, it will become apparent…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haste to the wedding (I): before the trip</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/09/haste-to-the-wedding-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/09/haste-to-the-wedding-i/</guid>
      <description>Well, the secret is out now, after being together 20 years, James and I eloped for a late-summer wedding overlooking the gorgeous Loch Lomond. And as we’ve been asked a few times what prompted this, a blog post seems in order. However, that’s not really so easy to write, not least because this is all quite personal. But, here we are with a little of the story…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
