<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>race report on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/race-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in race report on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/race-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LonDONE: a four-year marathon</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/londone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/londone/</guid>
      <description>I did it! That is, I finally completed the London marathon 21st April 2024, with a time of 6:33:02. Oh my gosh, has this ever been a lot of hard work – I’ve effectively trained for it three times after first the delays of the pandemic pushed it into 2023, then injury meaning I had to defer to 2024. So my initial reaction to crossing the line was really just one of relief&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandy 10 2023</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/04/sandy-10-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/04/sandy-10-2023/</guid>
      <description>I decided to enter the Sandy 10 this year after learning that it was the 40th anniversary of this race and realising that I had run the 30th anniversary race, which I think was my very first race as a member of NHRR&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonfire Burn 2022</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/11/bonfire-burn-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/11/bonfire-burn-2022/</guid>
      <description>When there’s a big banner for a 10 km race staring at you if you glance out of your office window, it does seem rude not to enter. Mind, this was back pre-pandemic in 2019, not long after I learnt I’d got a 2020 London marathon ballot place and at a point I could actually run a full 10 km&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herts Sunday cross country league 21/22 review</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/02/cross-country-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/02/cross-country-2021/</guid>
      <description>It was great news when I heard that the club had arranged for us to take part in the Herts Sunday cross country league, the winter sister competition to our usual summer interclub competition. As I prepared, I was very pleased to find that I&amp;rsquo;d had some forethought 2 years ago, and had loosened the spikes in the cross country shoes, so they weren’t rusted in place&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck n Dash 2021 (and 2024)</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/09/duck-n-dash-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/09/duck-n-dash-2021/</guid>
      <description>Today saw the return of the Duck n Dash aquathlon for its 11th year. This is an annual favourite for me, combining a 400 m lane swim in the Letchworth outdoor pool with a 5 km run round Norton Common&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
