<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Scotland on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/scotland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scotland on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/scotland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>West Highland Way (IV): Ben Nevis and home</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/08/west-highland-way-iv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/08/west-highland-way-iv/</guid>
      <description>Having reached Fort William in 5 days, I was definitely hoping to climb Ben Nevis but was a bit unsure whether it would be a good idea after the days spent hiking. After my first &amp;lsquo;full&amp;rsquo; breakfast of the trip  at the BnB, I decided to first deal with where my &amp;lsquo;no plan plan&amp;rsquo; was going to meet the rigid schedule of the railways&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Highland Way (III): Bridge of Orchy to the end</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/08/west-highland-way-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/08/west-highland-way-iii/</guid>
      <description>As we left the story of my adventure on the West Highland Way, it was 10 pm and I had just set up at the wild camping zone at the Bridge of Orchy having covered 104.3 km of the 154 km trail in 3 days of walking. This meant we now had the wildest section of the route to go&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Highland Way (II): the first three days to Bridge of Orchy</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/07/west-highland-way-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/07/west-highland-way-ii/</guid>
      <description>The West Highland Way is the UK’s most popular long-distance path. It’s not hard to work out why – it takes in some of the best of Scotland’s scenery, yet is fairly accessible hiking. Apparently, some 40,000 people complete the entire walk each year, and I was soon to be one of them&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Highland Way (I): preparation</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/06/west-highland-way-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/06/west-highland-way-prep/</guid>
      <description>I decided to walk the West Highland Way (running some 96 miles, or 154 km, from Milngavie, just north of Glasgow, to Fort William) after some original solo holiday plans fell through with a couple of months to go. I hence found myself trying to figure out what I&amp;rsquo;d need to do to walk a long-distance path at relatively short notice&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haste to the wedding (II): the day</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/10/haste-to-the-wedding-ii/</guid>
      <description>Where were we; oh yes, we were eloping to Scotland. Wow. It’s still a little scary to think it. And it’s getting even harder to write about. But here’s part two of the ‘haste to the wedding’ story, from leaving home until the end of the wedding day. And for those who don’t know the reason these posts are entitled ‘haste to the wedding’, it will become apparent…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haste to the wedding (I): before the trip</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/09/haste-to-the-wedding-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/09/haste-to-the-wedding-i/</guid>
      <description>Well, the secret is out now, after being together 20 years, James and I eloped for a late-summer wedding overlooking the gorgeous Loch Lomond. And as we’ve been asked a few times what prompted this, a blog post seems in order. However, that’s not really so easy to write, not least because this is all quite personal. But, here we are with a little of the story…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
