<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>graphic design on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/graphic-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graphic design on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/graphic-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An easy-to-print dated A5 planner: the script</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/10/planner-date-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/10/planner-date-script/</guid>
      <description>With a lot of hobbies, there’s always the bit that’s the chore. Maybe washing your brushes if you’re painting, figuring out code if you’re blogging, weighing the ingredients if you’re baking (endless washing if you’re running?). With making paper planners, it’s the dating, printing, cutting and punching&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constructing a personalised discbound planner</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/10/planner-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/10/planner-construction/</guid>
      <description>Although I love creative hobbies, time is always a factor that means I don’t do them as much as I like. A few years ago, I discovered decorative planning, and this led me into into exploring the concept of making my own personalised planner&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procreate with a Holly Pixel’s tutorial</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/06/procreate_tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/06/procreate_tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Text or other blocky elements entwined with background images is a look that’s often used in stickers and planners, and although it looks doable - it’s only combining a few elements together - I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even worked out how to use custom fonts on Procreate, let alone how to only show part of a rasterised text layer without just erasing. But now, after following along with a tutorial published by Holly Pixels (update from the future: no longer available), I&amp;rsquo;ve at least got somewhere on it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
