<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>blogging on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/blogging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blogging on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building an IndieWeb house (I): introduction</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2025/02/indieweb-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2025/02/indieweb-i/</guid>
      <description>When an email went round at work asking if anyone was up for giving a lunchtime talk on a hobby, I volunteered to do so. I’ve got to be honest that I did suspect ‘static site personal blogging’ might be considered a bit too esoteric for them to accept, but no, they took me up on it. Whelp! That’s now done, so, to record the details, I’m also writing it up as a few blog posts&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy blogiversary and  2 months on Mastodon</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/07/two-year-blogiversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/07/two-year-blogiversary/</guid>
      <description>It was ~2 years ago that we started this blog as a way to share long-form musings or the simple stuff going on on our lives with, well, with anyone who wanted to read it. Then, ~2 months ago, coffeenow also joined the fediverse and now has its own account on Mastodon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pitfalls of replacing an icon font with svg icons</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/04/svg-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2022/04/svg-icons/</guid>
      <description>This blog uses a fair few icons, such as the icons in the menu. Until today, these had been placed using a font kit from Font Awesome, which worked by using JavaScript to replace tags with the appropriate icon from their library. However, for some time I’d been wanting to move away from this method&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up the blog (II): initial design decisions</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/06/setting_up_blog_ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/06/setting_up_blog_ii/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post about setting up the blog, we were at the stage of having decided on, and got at least somewhere, with getting Hugo working to generate a website, but with much design still to do. And although design can be just going with your preferred template for the content, I want a little more input than that because I do just want a &amp;lsquo;feel&amp;rsquo; that says &amp;lsquo;coffee now&amp;rsquo; to me, like when you&amp;rsquo;re sat on the sofa with a coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up the blog (I): getting started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/05/setting_up_blog_i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/05/setting_up_blog_i/</guid>
      <description>When you make the decision to start a blog, one of the first things you need to consider is what sort of system you&amp;rsquo;re going to use to organise your content.
If you read any article on starting out blogging, it will almost certainly mention WordPress. WordPress (meaning software available at https://wordpress.org, not to be confused with WordPress.com; see below) is a very common open-source content management system (CMS) for creating websites, including, but far from limited to, those dedicated to blogging.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
