<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>London marathon on Coffee now</title>
    <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/london-marathon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London marathon on Coffee now</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/tags/london-marathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LonDONE: a four-year marathon</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/londone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/londone/</guid>
      <description>I did it! That is, I finally completed the London marathon 21st April 2024, with a time of 6:33:02. Oh my gosh, has this ever been a lot of hard work – I’ve effectively trained for it three times after first the delays of the pandemic pushed it into 2023, then injury meaning I had to defer to 2024. So my initial reaction to crossing the line was really just one of relief&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London marathon revisited: what if it goes right?</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/london2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2024/04/london2024/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m finally there&amp;hellip; that is past the longest run of training, past the last long run of tapering even, and it&amp;rsquo;s looking more likely than not that 2024 will be the year I really make it to the start line of the London marathon. It&amp;rsquo;s now ~1.5 weeks to go – I&amp;rsquo;m nervous, excited&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new running thing… but not in London</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/04/not-at-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/04/not-at-london/</guid>
      <description>Ok, so for those who don’t know, the London marathon didn’t happen for me this year. I think I’ve always been clear that there was a bit of an ‘if’ getting to the start line. When you are pushing yourself doing runs that are that far, there’s always a risk of picking up an injury&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Strava, I didn’t go that fast</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/01/not-that-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2023/01/not-that-fast/</guid>
      <description>It’s January. And, for a lot of people, at this time of year, there’s a renewed focus on fitness goals. This isn’t quite the case for me, as I’ve been training for the three-year marathon (yep, still plan to do it, injury excepting) since the start of October. Not quite training like I managed in 2019 and early 2020 but&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The three-year marathon?</title>
      <link>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/08/the-three-year-marathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coffeenow.moomop.uk/post/2021/08/the-three-year-marathon/</guid>
      <description>Getting a ballot place in the London marathon is a lucky thing. London marathon don&amp;rsquo;t publish the number of ballot places that they have, but estimates I&amp;rsquo;ve read say it&amp;rsquo;s ~17,000. We do know that there are usually ~40,000 runners&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
